Alter something in the past, and you'll change the future, usually.
With one exception. The timeline we know is made up of important notes.
You might accidentally alter something before one of these points,
but you're fine if the critical event still happens.
History will play out as it's supposed to.
Now, tragic news out of Fengqin.
At approximately 8.30 in the evening, an earthquake struck the county.
Its magnitude was 7.8, resulting in the mountain's collapse, among other disasters.
I'm here in Linjiang town, which was hit worst by the quake.
You can see that emergency workers are already on the scene. It's a monumental effort.
Rescuers arrived within four hours of the earthquake, and we're told many survivors have been found.
Unfortunately, it's impossible to know just how many people have been affected by this event.
So that's it. The reason you let me change things.
It doesn't matter what I tell them because they're all doomed.
They die in the quake, don't they?
Listen to me, Auntie. You have to stay here.
Huh? Hey, what'd you call me? Auntie?
It's dark outside. Where are you going?
Stop this. You can't save them. They're already dead.
Come back now before you make a terrible mistake!
Listen to me. Death is an important node that must not be changed.
No matter how hard this is, you can't alter their fates.
The chaos that would cause. Think, dammit!
The future that we now know could completely disappear.
You're hands are trembling so badly. It's been a hot day, but you're freezing. Do you think you're getting sick?
I'm okay.
Well, something's definitely not right.
You don't have a fever unless I've got one too.
No, I just forgot to tell Cap something important earlier. I'll be right back. So don't you worry.
But it's already getting dark out. Why don't you talk to them at school tomorrow?
W-Wait!
Lu, I know you said they're gone, but our hands were warm. It felt so real.
This isn't the way it's supposed to play out. If you start telling everyone about the earthquake, it'll cause a panic.
Things could play out worse than they already do.
It didn't take too long to realize something has changed in the back of my mind. Your eyes, there ain't nowhere left to hide behind. Time no longer flew like it was when the flash froze everything before. Without you, I don't know if I could take this road.
And I'm about to lose my mind. Every minute that I die back in time. Every single existence rewinds. Some physical pain in this eye drive. All mine. All the hardest and the smiles never faded. I know you'll be by my side when we make it. Come back from the times. Back in time.
Back in time.
Wind you have to blow gently tonight
Birds you have to sing softly and sweet
For now
For now my little baby is dreaming asleep
His eyes are just like his mother's, so bright
You're naive. Basketball won't put food on the table so I'm not cooking for you. Hear me?
From now on you can buy your own meal. Fine by me. I'll starve
Huh? What's going on here? Luong Ben is usually such a reliable kid. Is he in trouble? Bad news?
He's a growing boy, you know. He needs hearty meals
These kids are obsessed with playing basketball. I don't get it
Oh, hey, why are you here? Hurry
Run away! Are you nuts? My knee is still busted. I can't
Chen Xiao? He's already hurt and you want to make it worse? Are you the one to blame for his injury?
No, I... that's not the case. Everyone's in danger
What are you trying to pull here? Start talking, young man
Yeah, gotta admit I'm confused
Just go! Take your sister and get as far away from this town as you can! Please!
Let me guess, you want some more secret practice? The next tournament's in two weeks. There's plenty of time
There's no team anymore! The school already decided to tear down the court! Today was our last game!
What? Teach didn't mention that! You're lying! I swear! That's enough! Go back home! I'm only trying to help you guys!
I see how it is! You have one good game and suddenly you think you're in charge!
Hey! Calm down, please! I'm sure there's a good reason he's here!
Tonight at 8.30! There'll be an earthquake! Hey! Your dad's in the city! You need to call us! Tell him you're ready to move in now!
Have you been contacting your father behind my back making plans to move away?
No! I haven't decided yet!
You little sneak! You want to go to the city, huh? Is that why he's here? If you choose to follow this heartless bastard then I'll disown you!
She just said she hasn't decided! So grateful! Both of you! One of you wants to play games in the city! The other wants to study there! But who cares what your mother might want?
Enough! You're making a scene! Perfect! Why don't we let our neighbors decide who's right and who's wrong here?
Your actions could cause pandemonium, making the timeline unpredictable.
You can't save those who die tonight. But it's quite possible you could get more people killed. Be smart.
What was that he said about an earthquake? Where'd he hear that? Can't be true.
Although it does feel strange tonight. So hot outside. Could that be a sign? An omen?
My dog barked the entire day. Mine did the same. Like you were scared. That sounds like a premonition to me.
They say dogs have a sixth sense about these things.
Shenzhou, how in the hell would you know there's going to be an earthquake?
Well, I...
Um...
Yeah, where'd you hear such a story? If it's real, we need to evacuate. Better to be cautious.
You shouldn't go spreading wild rumors and scaring the whole town.
Yes, no need to be, Janet. Things aren't always bad.
Just be a small... Start talking! Now!
You don't want to be caught on thought. At least pack something.
I'm sure I trust you.
What is happening?
I read about it! In a magazine!
The poor kid took it seriously. Got us all scared for nothing. Very true. Imagine we would have looked like utter fools.
Oh, going already? Make sure you study hard and exercise that brain of yours. Maybe that way this won't happen to you again.
It won't happen to you again.
I want to save these people. It's not fair!
We can't do that. It's their fate. They die. Stay strong. Keep going.
One person. You have to let me save his mother.
Please, I'm begging you. There has to be a way that she can survive.
Alright. I'll tell you what to do.
Thank you, Lu.
Earthquake?
That's right. I heard about it when I went to Lu Hongbin's. The whole town's freaking out, so we've got to get out of here fast!
We can't just leave. At least let me throw some stuff in a bag.
There's no time to pack!
The earthquake causes a mountain to collapse. It buries half the town, which means it'll be too dangerous to be outside.
Our client was only saved because he huddled in his dining room.
Hey. You still mad at Mom?
No. I'm just looking at the sky. Looks pretty tonight, right?
Here. She told me to bring you some rice.
Not hungry.
So stubborn that you'll starve yourself.
So what does Chen Xiao think about you studying in the city?
I don't know and I don't care.
Why did you tell him then?
It's past eight. Do your homework without my help.
There will be an earthquake tonight at 8.30!
We won't need this stuff if we're dead. Take this seriously.
Okay, I hear you. I'm almost done.
Your time is up. You gotta move.
Son, wait! What's gotten into you?
Hey, sis. That earthquake. It was just a story, right?
You know, for a second there, I actually believed this little prank of yours.
Aren't you getting too old to be playing hide and seek?
What's happening? Shouldn't we feel shaken right now?
Oh, wait. I forgot something important.
No! Don't! I'll go get it for you.
Mom!
Are you all right, son?
Yeah, I'm good.
You?
I'm fine.
Just a little tired.
I need to rest.
Remember, if this is too hard for you, you can always jump out.
Don't be afraid.
Your mama's right here to keep you safe.
I'm sorry, son.
I hope that you know just how much you mean to me.
We've had some hard times.
My temper was short.
You're killing our son!
I only know a few recipes to pass on.
The ones your father loved.
I never studied a lot.
There isn't much else I can teach you.
The only thing I can do is support my two favorite people.
So you can live the lives you want to lead.
Honey, if you like sports, then go play them.
And move to the city if that's what you dream of.
Please don't blame me for being selfish.
I'm just scared to think of you leaving home.
It's natural.
I can imagine your face right now.
When you were so tiny.
And you needed me to take care of you.
And you have to blow gently tonight.
Because you have to see me.
It was me, Mom.
I'm scared.
Mommy's here.
You'll be safe.
I promise.
Rest your eyes.
For now, my little baby is asleep and dreaming.
His eyes are just like his mother's.
So bright.
And his eyes are just like his mother's.
And he'll see you later.
Bye.
Mom?
No.
Please.
Stay.
You have to stay with me.
I'm scared of the dark.
I don't want to be loved.
I think I heard someone cry.
You have to help us, please!
Don't worry.
Wake up.
They're gonna save you.
Everything's gonna be okay.
We've got two people down here.
Slow and steady.
Make sure the rock doesn't collapse.
Please, sir, you have to stay back.
This is my house, dammit!
My family might be inside!
Rescuers arrived within four hours of the earthquake,
and we're told many survivors have been found.
Unfortunately, it's impossible to...
My mom's down there, too.
You have to go get her.
Please take a deep breath and calm down.
We'll do everything we can for her.
I promise you.
She's still alive.
You just have to wake her up.
Help her!
Save her!
This is where we part.
Farewell, my dearest.
I'm sorry.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you want his mom to die?
So that the future wouldn't change.
I'm sorry.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you want his mom to die?
So that the future wouldn't change.
I'm sorry.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you want his mom to die?
So that the future wouldn't change.
The future wouldn't change.
I don't understand.
I don't understand. What was the point of delivering all those messages if we didn't end up saving anyone?
You know, after all these years, I still wonder what would have happened if I'd caught an earlier bus.
I might have been able to help save her.
Listen, you know the rules. We go to the past, but we leave it like we found it.
I ran across this while I was cleaning the house yesterday, buried in a box. I thought it was destroyed, but...
Hi, um, are you able to develop pictures from an older camera here?
Sure. What kind of film are we talking?
And... well, it's actually still inside the camera.
Right here.
Huh?
Don't question what's happened, or the future will be altered.
Because of us.
It's a little beaten up, but maybe the film's okay.
Oh, wait. I forgot something important.
No! Don't! I'll go get it for you.
Grab your dad's camera, and come right back.
Captain, I have to tell you.
I've been dreaming about the game with Longyang recently.
I get subbed in.
I dunk and throw three-pointers, and we end up winning.
Then I wake up, missing the days when we could play together.
I'm old now, and make it to the court when I can.
It's not the same without you guys, though.
The teammates who joked about me not shooting well, but were still willing to pass me the ball during games.
Basketball will never be the same for me.
Ever.
So?
Shen Chiao!
How about a game?
Come on!
Get over here!
Thank you, Captain.
You've given me treasured memories of a true friendship.
Hey, what's the deal with the distance?
Let's go, Jen, would you?
When I heard you wanted to go to the city, I was really happy for you, even if it meant you leaving, and us being apart.
The city has better schools, and more chances for people to grow.
I wish you'd left right then.
That day when we talked, if only you had, I'd have worked to get into a school there, too.
If you, we'd be reunited, I would catch up to you.
Pinky promise.
Mom, I'm mostly just be taking pictures for the school paper.
It's no big deal.
This was your dad's first camera.
Be careful with it.
He loved that thing.
Takes great pics.
Took me half a year to save up the money for it, you know.
But I thought you hated dad's photography.
Yeah, it does drive me crazy.
Always taking pictures of others.
Here, snap one of your mom.
See if it still works.
Make it a good one.
Kiss me.
Wind, you have to blow gently tonight, birds, you have to sing softly and sweet.
And little baby's mouth is just like his mom and dad.
What are you two doing, huh? Don't you have work?
I think we need a break. Trust me, it'll end up being good for business in the long run.
And you agree? You're pooped out too?
Fine rest. Just give me a heads up when you're done.
Excuse me. I'm looking for an old witch who can enter the past through photos.
Nope. There's no such thing here. Definitely no one old. I'm sorry to disappoint you, but best of luck on your search.
I'm with the police.
I got lost in this street that I'm living in.
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking.
Let me O zur the opposite.
I got lost in the street and I'm living it.
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking.
I see my hand,
and my arm is still alive.
The only thing I've seen in my head
is that my eyes are still alive?
You should really stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it.
Stop stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
To be left,
the dream of the dream of the world,
the dream of the world.
I need to do it again so that I can't.
So stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it.
Stop stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
In this time,
the dream of the dream of the world.
I understand
how many of the worries
are still alive.
Stop thinking about it.
Stop stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
Yeah.